<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<languages>

	
	<!--ENGLISH-->
	<language>
		<Name>English</Name>
		<Bonjour>Hello</Bonjour>
		<Aurevoir>bye</Aurevoir>
		
		<textSounds>SOUNDS</textSounds>
		<textMusic>MUSIC</textMusic>
		<textLanguage>LANGUAGES</textLanguage>
		<textBack>BACK</textBack>
	
		<textTuto>TUTORIAL</textTuto>
		<textSettings>SETTINGS</textSettings>
		<textLeave>QUIT</textLeave>
		<textForfeit>FORFEIT</textForfeit>
		<textContinue>CONTINUE</textContinue>
		<oui>brrrrrrrrr</oui>
		<textDialogue>NO TEXT</textDialogue>

		<textTitle>NAME :</textTitle>

		<!-- Description carte-->
		<simpleShot>DESTROY A TILE</simpleShot>
		<probe>LETS YOU SHOOT THREE PROBES THAT WON'T DAMAGE THE ENEMY SPACESHIP BUT WILL REVEAL THE SELECTED TILES</probe>
		<emp> SHOOTS A BEAM THAT WILL DESTROY THE TARGET AND MAKE THE SURROUNDING ROOMS INACTIVE FOR 1 TURN</emp>
		<timeAccelerator>A JUMP IN TIME THAT WILL REDUCE ALL YOUR COOLDOWNS BY 1</timeAccelerator>
		<capacitor>THIS ABILITY WILL UPGRADE YOUR NEXT SIMPLE HIT SHOT TO A MASSIVE CUBE SHOT OF 2 BY 2 FOR THE NEXT TURN ONLY</capacitor>
		<alternateShot>SHOOTS IN A ROW OF 3 TILES THEN CHANGES FOR ITS NEXT USE THIS ABILITY TO SHOOT IN A COLUMN OF 3 TILES</alternateShot>
		<upgradeShot>REVEAL ONE TILE THEN UPGRADES ITSELF - DESTROY ONE TILE THEN UPGRADES ITSELF - DESTROY 3 TILES IN A DIAGONAL THEN UPGRADES ITSELF - DESTROY 5 TILES IN A CROSS PATTERN</upgradeShot>
		<scanner>REVEALS AN ENTIRE COLUMN OF TILES</scanner>
		<energyDecoy>REVEAL A RANDOM ROOM TILE AND WHEN IT’S DESTROYED IT WILL GIVE 1 ENERGY FOR THE NEXT TURN ; IT WILL RESPAWN AT A RANDOM PLACE AFTER IT‘S DESTROYED</energyDecoy>
		<timeDecoy>REVEAL A RANDOM ROOM TILE AND WHEN IT’S DESTROYED IT WILL INCREASE THE COOLDOWN BY 1 OF THE ABILITY THAT DESTROYED IT ; IT WILL RESPAWN AT A RANDOM PLACE AFTER IT‘S DESTROYED</timeDecoy>
		<repairDecoy>REVEAL A RANDOM ROOM TILE AND WHEN IT’S DESTROYED IT WILL REPAIR A RANDOM ROOM; IT WILL RESPAWN AT A RANDOM PLACE AFTER IT‘S DESTROYED</repairDecoy>
		<randomReveal>REVEALS 5 EMPTY TILES AT RANDOM PLACES IN THE ENEMY SHIP.</randomReveal>
		
		<AbilityDescription>No description</AbilityDescription>
		<AbilityName>No name</AbilityName>
		<RoomName>No name</RoomName>

		<!--UI Fight-->
		<changeViewEnemy>SEE ENEMY SPACESHIP</changeViewEnemy>
		<changeViewPlayer>SEE YOUR SPACESHIP</changeViewPlayer>
		<warning>WARNING</warning>
		<enemyLife>ENEMY LIFE</enemyLife>
		<yourLife>MY LIFE</yourLife>
		<endTurn>END TURN</endTurn>
		<Fire>FIRE !</Fire>
		<ready>READY</ready>

		<Player1>Player 1</Player1>
		<Player2>Player 2</Player2>

		<!--Card title -->
		<titleSimpleShot>SIMPLE SHOT</titleSimpleShot>
		<titleProbe>PROBE</titleProbe>
		<titleEmp>EMP</titleEmp>
		<titleTimeAccelerator>TIME ACCELERATOR</titleTimeAccelerator>
		<titleCapacitor>CAPACITOR</titleCapacitor>
		<titleAlternateShot>ALTERNATE SHOT</titleAlternateShot>
		<titleUpgradeShot>UPGRADE SHOT</titleUpgradeShot>
		<titlescanner>SCANNER</titlescanner>
		<titleEnergyDecoy>ENERGY DECOY</titleEnergyDecoy>
		<titleTimeDecoy>TIME DECOY</titleTimeDecoy>
		<titleRepairDecoy>REPAIR DECOY</titleRepairDecoy>
		<titleRandomReveal>RANDOM REVEAL</titleRandomReveal>
		
		<!--Room title-->
		<titleGenerator>GENERATOR</titleGenerator>
		<titleCockpit>COCKPIT</titleCockpit>

		<!--UI Draft-->
		<selectSpaceShip>SELECT A SPACESHIP</selectSpaceShip>
		<selectRooms>SELECT ROOMS</selectRooms>
		<Next>NEXT</Next>

		<!--UI Construct-->
		<randomizeRooms>Randomize your rooms</randomizeRooms>
		<timeRemaning>remaning</timeRemaning>
		
				<!--Voice lines : N=Nerd,C=Cowboy, R=Chef -->
			<!--Hit-->
		<voiceHitN2>DEBUG.LOG("PANIK");</voiceHitN2>
		<voiceHitN3>ERROR 404 => ROOM NOT FOUND !</voiceHitN3>
		<voiceHitN4>PUTTING UP A FIGHT HUH.. (ง・.・)ง</voiceHitN4>

		<voiceHitC1>I MIGHT BE GETTING TOO RUSTY FOR THIS…</voiceHitC1>
		<voiceHitC2>DARN YOUNGLINGS DON’T KNOW HOW TO TREAT ROBOTS MY AGE</voiceHitC2>
		<voiceHitC3>THIS IS JUST A BULLET WOUND…</voiceHitC3>
		<voiceHitC4>WAIT ! THE SUN WAS IN MY EYE-CAPTORS-</voiceHitC4>

		<voiceHitR1>OH NO ! YOU ALMOST-A MADE MY BEAUTIFUL RAVIOLI SLIP!</voiceHitR1>
		
			<!--Attack-->
		<voiceAttackN1>PRINT(“FIRE, DEATH AND CATZ :3 !!!”);</voiceAttackN1>
		<voiceAttackN2>NATURAL 20 !!!.! (*W*)</voiceAttackN2>
		<voiceAttackN3>LET’S SPEEDRUN THIS FIGHT (>WO)~~~**</voiceAttackN3>

		<voiceAttackC1>TELL ME NOW, HOW DOES MY IRON-RAILGUN TASTE ?</voiceAttackC1>
		<voiceAttackC2>YOU ATTACKED THE WRONG BOT, KIDDO</voiceAttackC2>
		<voiceAttackC3>YOU WOULDN’T LAST A DAY IN THE GALACTIC FAR WEST</voiceAttackC3>

		<voiceAttackR1>TIME FOR-A THE BILL !</voiceAttackR1>
		<voiceAttackR2>AW, YOU LOOK-A HUNGRY ! HAVE-A SOME RAVIOLI !</voiceAttackR2>
		<voiceAttackR3>WATCH OUT FOR THIS-A ONE !</voiceAttackR3>
		
			<!--Victory-->
		<voiceVictoryN1>GGEZ BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME \(^U^)/ !</voiceVictoryN1>
		<voiceVictoryN2>SORRY FOR THE BLUE SCREEN IV</voiceVictoryN2>
		<voiceVictoryN3>GET PWND NOOB !</voiceVictoryN3>
		<voiceVictoryN4>HOPE YOUR NEXT OPPONENT ISN'T AS GOOD AS ME ;3</voiceVictoryN4>
		<voiceVictoryN5>ENJOY THE KILLCAM 乁(^◞ ^)ㄏ</voiceVictoryN5>

		<voiceVictoryC1>I’M GOOD, YOU MIGHT BE BAD… BUT YOU’RE SURE AS SPACE UGLY..</voiceVictoryC1>
		<voiceVictoryC2>STILL A GOOD SHOT DESPITE MY OLD AGE..</voiceVictoryC2>
		<voiceVictoryC3>TIS’ HIGH NOON SOMEWHERE IN THE GALAXY…</voiceVictoryC3>

		<voiceVictoryR1>AWW GO BACK AND-A CRY TO YOUR-A MAMMA !</voiceVictoryR1>
		<voiceVictoryR2>YOU WEREN’T SEASONED WELL ENOUGH TO BE SERVED, BAMBINO</voiceVictoryR2>
		<voiceVictoryR3>IL CAPO ALWAYS-A WINS !</voiceVictoryR3>

		<textWin>Win</textWin>

		<!--Tuto-->
		<textTuto1>HERE YOU WILL BE ABLE TO CHOOSE A ROOM TO ADD IN YOUR SPACESHIP. EACH ROOM IS LINKED TO AN ABILITY, SO IF A ROOM IS DESTROYED YOU WILL LOOSE THE CAPACITY</textTuto1>
		<textTuto2>THIS IS YOUR SPACESHIP. DOWN THERE YOU HAVE A REMINDER OF THE ROOM YOU ALREADY CHOSE</textTuto2>
		<textTuto3>YOUR ENEMY WILL HAVE THE SAME OPTIONS AS YOU SO DON’T FORGET TO THINK AHEAD AND MAKE SMART DECISION</textTuto3>
		<textTuto4>HERE YOU CAN ARRANGE THE ROOMS YOU CHOSE TO PREPARE YOURSELF FOR THE FIGHT.</textTuto4>
		<textTuto5>TO WIN YOU WILL NEED TO ANNIHILATE THE ENEMY SPACESHIP BY DESTROYING ALL OF HIS VITAL ROOMS. HERE YOU CAN SEE HOW MANY VITALS ARE LEFT TO DESTROY, IN RED, YOUR ENNEMY’S AND IN BLUE, YOURS</textTuto5>
		<textTuto6>THOSE ARE YOUR ABILITIES EACH OF THEM WILL NEED A ENERGY TO BE USE AND MOST OF THEM WILL HAVE A COOLDOWN REPRESENTED BY A CLOCK ON TOP OF IT’S CARD.</textTuto6>
		<textTuto7>EVERY ROOM IS ATTACHED TO AN ABILITY, IF THE ROOM IS ENTIRELY DESTROYED, THE CAPACITY LINKED TO IT WILL BE DEACTIVATED</textTuto7>
		<textTuto8>THIS IS A RECAP OF THE ENEMY ACTIONS WERE YOU CAN LOOK AT THE EFFECTS OF ENEMY ABILTY</textTuto8>
	

</language>

<!--FRENCH-->
	<language>
		<Name>Français</Name>
		<Bonjour>Bonjour</Bonjour>
		<Aurevoir>Aurevoir</Aurevoir>
		
		<textSounds>SONS</textSounds>
		<textMusic>MUSIQUE</textMusic>
		<textLanguage>LANGAGES</textLanguage>
		<textBack>RETOUR</textBack>
	
		<textTuto>TUTORIEL</textTuto>
		<textSettings>PARAMETRES</textSettings>
		<textLeave>QUITTER</textLeave>
		<textForfeit>ABANDONNER</textForfeit>
		<textContinue>CONTINUER</textContinue>
		<oui>boooooo</oui>
		<textDialogue>PAS DE TEXTE</textDialogue>

		<textTitle>NOM :</textTitle>
		
		<!-- Description carte-->
		<simpleShot>DÉTRUIT UNE CASE</simpleShot>
		<probe>LANCE UNE SALVE DE 3 TIRS DANS UNE ZONE CIBLÉE QUI NE VONT PAS FAIRE DE DÉGÂTS MAIS VONT RÉVÉLER DES CASES</probe>
		<emp>TIR QUI VA DÉTRUIRE LA SALLE CIBLÉE ET RENDRE INACTIVE LES SALLES AUTOURS POUR 1 TOUR</emp>
		<timeAccelerator>UN SAUT DANS LE TEMPS QUI VA RÉDUIRE VOS COOLDOWNS DE 1</timeAccelerator>
		<capacitor>CETTE CAPACITÉE VA AMÉLIORER VOTRE PROCHAIN TIR SIMPLE EN UN TIR DE 2 PAR 2 POUR LE PROCHAIN TOUR UNIQUEMENT</capacitor>
		<alternateShot>TIR SUR 3 CASES À LA VERTICALE PUIS AU PROCHAIN CHANGE DE SENS</alternateShot>
		<upgradeShot>RÉVÈLE UNE CASE PUIS S'AMÉLIORE - DÉTRUIT UNE CASE PUIS S'AMÉLIORE - DÉTRUIT 3 CASES EN DIAGONALES PUIS S'AMÉLIORE - DÉTRUIT 5 CASE EN FORME DE CROIX</upgradeShot>
		<scanner>RÉVÈLE LES SALLES SUR UNE COLONNE</scanner>
		<energyDecoy>RÉVÈLE UNE CASE DE SALLE. SI CETTE SALLE EST TOUCHÉE ELLE VA VOUS DONNER UN D'ÉNERGIE EN PLUS POUR LE PROCHAIN TOUR PUIS RÉAPPARAIT SUR UNE CASE VIDE ALÉATOIRE</energyDecoy>
		<timeDecoy>RÉVÈLE UNE CASE DE SALLE. SI CETTE SALLE EST TOUCHÉE ELLE VA AUGMENTÉ LE COOLDOWN DE LA CAPACITÉ UTILISÉ DE 1 (NE MARCHE PAS SUR LE TIR DE BASE) PUIS RÉAPPARAIT SUR UNE CASE VIDE ALÉATOIRE</timeDecoy>
		<repairDecoy>RÉVÈLE UNE CASE DE SALLE. SI CETTE SALLE EST TOUCHÉE ELLE VA RÉPARER UNE SALLE DÉTRUITE ALÉATOIRE PUIS RÉAPPARAIT SUR UNE CASE VIDE ALÉATOIRE</repairDecoy>
		<randomReveal>RÉVÈLE 5 CASES VIDES À DES ENDROITS ALÉATOIRES DU VAISSEAU ENNEMI.</randomReveal>
		
		<AbilityDescription>Pas description</AbilityDescription>
		<AbilityName>Pas de nom</AbilityName>
		<RoomName>Pas de nom</RoomName>
		
		
		<!--UI Fight-->
		<changeViewEnemy>VOIR LE VAISSEAU ENNEMI</changeViewEnemy>
		<changeViewPlayer>VOIR VOTRE VAISSEAU</changeViewPlayer>
		<warning>Attention</warning>
		<enemyLife>Vie ennemi</enemyLife>
		<yourLife>Ta vie</yourLife>
		<endTurn>Fin de tour</endTurn>
		<Fire>Feu !</Fire>
		<ready>PRÊT</ready>
		
		<Player1>Joueur 1</Player1>
		<Player2>Joueur 2</Player2>
		
		<!--Card title -->
		<titleSimpleShot>TIR SIMPLE</titleSimpleShot>
		<titleProbe>SONDE</titleProbe>
		<titleEmp>IEM</titleEmp>
		<titleTimeAccelerator>ACCÉLÉRATEUR TEMPOREL</titleTimeAccelerator>
		<titleCapacitor>CONDENSATEUR</titleCapacitor>
		<titleAlternateShot>TIR ALTERNÉ</titleAlternateShot>
		<titleUpgradeShot>TIR AMÉLIORÉ</titleUpgradeShot>
		<titlescanner>SCANNEUR</titlescanner>
		<titleEnergyDecoy>LEURRE ÉNERGÉTIQUE</titleEnergyDecoy>
		<titleTimeDecoy>LEURRE TEMPOREL</titleTimeDecoy>
		<titleRepairDecoy>LEURRE RÉPARATEUR</titleRepairDecoy>
		<titleRandomReveal>RÉVÉLATION ALÉATOIRE</titleRandomReveal>

		<!--Room title-->
		<titleGenerator>GENERATEUR</titleGenerator>
		<titleCockpit>POSTE DE PILOTAGE</titleCockpit>


		<!--UI Draft-->
		<selectSpaceShip>SÉLECTIONNÉ UN VAISSEAU</selectSpaceShip>
		<selectRooms>SÉLECTIONNÉ UNE SALLE</selectRooms>
		<Next>SUIVANT</Next>
		
		<!--UI Construct-->
		<randomizeRooms>ALÉATOIRISÉ LES SALLES</randomizeRooms>
		<timeRemaning>RESTANT</timeRemaning>
		
		<textWin>VICTOIRE</textWin>
		
		<!--Voice lines : N=Nerd,C=Cowboy, R=Chef -->
			<!--Hit-->
		<voiceHitN2>DEBUG.LOG("PANIQUE");</voiceHitN2>
		<voiceHitN3>ERREUR 404 => SALLE INTROUVABLE !</voiceHitN3>
		<voiceHitN4>TU SAIS TE BATTRE DIS DONC (ง・.・)ง</voiceHitN4>

		<voiceHitC1>JE SUIS TROP ROUILLÉ POUR FAIRE ÇA</voiceHitC1>
		<voiceHitC2>DIS DONC LES JEUNES DE NOS JOURS NE SAVENT PAS COMMENT SE COMPORTER AVEC LES ROBOTS DE MON ÂGE</voiceHitC2>
		<voiceHitC3>C'EST JUSTE UNE BALLE DANS MON BUSTE...</voiceHitC3>
		<voiceHitC4>ATTENDS !J'AI LE SOLEIL DANS MES CAPTEURS VISUELS</voiceHitC4>

		<voiceHitR1>OH NON! T'AS PRESQUE FAIT TOMBER MES MAGNIFIIIIQUES RAVIOLIS!</voiceHitR1>
		
			<!--Attack-->
		<voiceAttackN1>PRINT("FEU,MORT ET CHAT :3 !!!");</voiceAttackN1>
		<voiceAttackN2>UN 20 NATUREL !!.! (*W*)</voiceAttackN2>
		<voiceAttackN3>ON VA SPEEDRUN CE COMBAT (>WO)~~~**</voiceAttackN3>

		<voiceAttackC1>TU PEUX ME DIRE QUEL GOÛT À MON REVOLVER-RAILGUN?</voiceAttackC1>
		<voiceAttackC2>TU T'ES ATTAQUÉ AU MAUVAIS ROBOT MON PTIT</voiceAttackC2>
		<voiceAttackC3>TU NE SURVIVRAI PAS UN SEUL JOUR DANS LA GALAXIE DU FAR WEST</voiceAttackC3>

		<voiceAttackR1>C'EST L'HEURE DE L'A.D.I.T.I.O.N</voiceAttackR1>
		<voiceAttackR2>AW, T'AS L'AIR D'AVOIR FAIM! PENDS QUELQOUNE RAVIOLIII !</voiceAttackR2>
		<voiceAttackR3>FAIS GAFFE À CELUI-CI</voiceAttackR3>
		
			<!--Victory-->
		<voiceVictoryN1>GGEZ TU SERAS PEUT-ÊTRE PLUS CHANCEUX LA PROCHAINE FOIS \(^U^)/ !</voiceVictoryN1>
		<voiceVictoryN2>DÉSOLÉ POUR LE SCREEN BLUE |V</voiceVictoryN2>
		<voiceVictoryN3>VA FALLOIR QUE TU PEXES LE NOOB!</voiceVictoryN3>
		<voiceVictoryN4>J'ESPÈRE QUE TON PROCHAIN ADVERSAIRE N'EST PAS AUSSI BON QUE MOI ;3</voiceVictoryN4>
		<voiceVictoryN5>BONNE KILLCAM乁(^◞ ^)ㄏ</voiceVictoryN5>

		<voiceVictoryC1>NON CETTE GALAXIE N'EST PAS POUR UN VIEL ROBOT COMME TOI!</voiceVictoryC1>
		<voiceVictoryC2>JE SUIS TOUJOURS AUSSI PRÉCIS MALGRÉ MON VIEL ÂGE</voiceVictoryC2>
		<voiceVictoryC3>UNE DERNIÈRE VOLONTÉE AVANT DE QUITTER CETTE GALAXIE?</voiceVictoryC3>

		<voiceVictoryR1>AWW RETOURNE PLEURER DANS LES JOUPONS DE TA MAMMA!</voiceVictoryR1>
		<voiceVictoryR2>TU N'ÉTAIS PAS ASSEZ BIEN ASSAISONER POUR ÊTRE SERVIS, BAMBINO</voiceVictoryR2>
		<voiceVictoryR3>IL CAPO GAGNE TOUJOURS!!</voiceVictoryR3>

		<!--Tuto-->
		<textTuto1>DANS CE MENU, VOUS POUVEZ CHOISIR DES SALLES À AJOUTER À VOTRE VAISSEAU. CHAQUE PIÈCE EST LIÉE À UNE CAPACITÉ QUE VOUS POURREZ UTILISER, MAIS SI LA SALLE EST DÉTRUITE, LA CAPACITÉ SERA DÉSACTIVÉE.</textTuto1>
		<textTuto2>ICI, VOUS POUVEZ VOIR VOTRE VAISSEAU, ET EN DESSOUS, UNE LISTE DES SALLES QUE VOUS AVEZ DÉJÀ CHOISIES.</textTuto2>
		<textTuto3>VOTRE ADVERSAIRE AURA LES MÊMES PROPOSITIONS QUE VOUS, DONC RAPPELEZ-VOUS EN POUR FAIRE LE CHOIX LE PLUS RÉFLÉCHI.</textTuto3>
		<textTuto4>DANS CE MENU, VOUS POUVEZ DÉPLACER VOS PIÈCES POUR VOUS PRÉPARER À RECEVOIR LES ATTAQUES ADVERSES.</textTuto4>
		<textTuto5>POUR GAGNER, VOUS DEVREZ ANNIHILER LE VAISSEAU ENNEMI EN DÉTRUISANT TOUTES SES SALLES VITALES. VOUS POUVEZ VOIR LE NOMBRE DE SALLES VITALES RESTANTES À VOTRE ADVERSAIRE EN ROUGE, ET LES VOTRES EN BLEU.</textTuto5>
		<textTuto6>ICI, VOUS VOYEZ VOS CAPACITÉS, CHACUNE PRENDRA UNE ÉNERGIE À ÊTRE LANCÉE ET AURA UN COOLDOWN INDICAT AVEC LE CHRONOMÈTRE AU DESSUS DE SA CARTE.</textTuto6>
		<textTuto7>CHAQUE SALLE EST ASSOCIÉE À UNE CAPACITÉ, SI LA SALLE EST ENTIÈREMENT DÉTRUITE, LA CAPACITÉ LIÉE SERA INUTILISABLE.</textTuto7>
		<textTuto8>ICI VOUS POUVEZ VOIR UN RÉCAP DES ACTIONS ENNEMIS SUR LEQUEL VOUS POUVEZ APPUYER POUR SAVOIR COMMENT ELLES MARCHENT.</textTuto8>

	
</language>
</languages>